#### **ABOUT ME**

Having five years of professional experience in website's content management I decided to learn also how to create websites and applications from scratch. I learned a lot during courses and on my own and now my goal is to apply my knowledge as Front-End Developer and learn more as a member of a team.



#### **COURSES**

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER BOOTCAMP

01.2017 - 03.2017

Programming course, Coders Lab – Coding Bootcamp

- Languages HTML5, CSS3, Sass, JavaScript 5 & 6
- Libraries jQuery, React.js
- Design techniques Responsive Web Design
- Tools Git, Github, Gulp.js, Webpack
- Systems Ubuntu Linux

#### WEB DEVELOPER BOOTCAMP

2016

Online course (Udemy.com) - 40 h

- Languages HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript 5
- Libraries jQuery
- Tools Git, Github
- Frameworks- Bootstrap

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **CONTENT MANAGER / PROJECT COORDINATOR** 07.2011 – 12.2016

Fabryka Komunikacji Społecznej

- Managing the website kampaniespoleczne.pl using Content Managment System
- Technical support for website users
- Creating and sending the newsletter based on HTML
- Cooperating with external suppliers of IT solutions
- Recruiting and coordinating work of website's journalists
- Coordinating media patronages
- Representing kampaniespoleczne.pl in other media (radio, internet media)
- Co-coordinating the organisation of annual contest Public Service Ad of the Year (2011-2015)

### JUNIOR PROJECT COORDINATOR & EDITOR

12.2009 - 02.2011

Fabryka Komunikacji Społecznej

### **EDUCATION**

### UNIWERSYTET WARSZAWSKI

2013

Institute of Applied Polish Studies – Proofreading and editing (postgraduate studies)

## UNIVERSIDAD DE GRANADA

2011

Facultad de Ciencias Politicas y Sociologia – Sociology (Erasmus exchange programme)

#### **UNIWERSYTET WARSZAWSKI**

2010 - 2012

Institute of Applied Social Sciences – Sociology, Master's degree

### **UNIWERSYTET WARSZAWSKI**

2007 - 2010

Institute of Applied Social Sciences - Sociology, Bachelor's degree

#### **SKILLS**

- English level C2 (Certificate in Advanced English, grade A)
- Spanish level C1 (Diploma de Espanol como Lengua Extranjera C1)
- Microsoft Windows and Office, Photoshop, Wordpress

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the Personal Data Protection Act as of 29 August 1997, consolidated text: Journal of Laws 2016, item 922 as amended.